Kristiyan Nedyalkov

% +359894741497 in LinkedIn Portfolio C GitHub I like to work with people who... Current role Full Stack Engineer at Myra Security Are generally fun to be around. I find that a good Experience Cyber Security, Healthcare, Mental health atmosphere makes everyone more proactive and happy at work. **Technologies** React, Node.js, Apollo, Next.js, Gatsby, Laravel, React Native, Java, Kotlin, Ruby on Rails

Work experience

Full Stack Engineer, Myra Security

Oct 2022 - Present (10m)

Security as a Service provider Cyber Security

React Node.js

Apollo

Next.js

Gatsby

Laravel

- Designed and developed a new marketing website, driving brand awareness and lead generation.
- · Enhanced team productivity by contributing to the creation of an internal UI component library.
- Enabled seamless transition to a microservice architecture through the development of a GraphQL proxy.

Software Developer, Sanvello

Aug 2020 - Oct 2022 (2y 2m)

Self-Care mental wellbeing Healthcare · Mental health

React

React Native

Java

Kotlin

Ruby on Rails

- Developed and launched a responsive, accessible React web application, driving an improved user experience and increased customer satisfaction.
- Collaborated in the creation and development of a feature-rich React admin panel, empowering the team with advanced capabilities for efficient management and oversight.
- Led the successful rewrite of an Android app using React Native, resulting in enhanced performance and expanded market reach.
- Contributed to Java, Kotlin, and Ruby on Rails codebases, actively shaping the development and innovation
 of various core components.

Education

Plovdivski Universitet 'Paisii Hilendarski'

Oct 2017 - Jun 2021 (3y 8m)

Bachelors Psychology

 While not necessarily related to Software Development, my Psychology degree has been instrumental in developing a solid set of soft skills.

Snippets

Portfolio w kestenbok.github.io

My personal, terminal themed, portfolio

More about me

I like to work with people who...

Are generally fun to be around. I find that a good atmosphere makes everyone more proactive and happy at work.

Outside of work I...

Recently started being more active again, after becoming a bit of a homebody during the lockdowns. I've picked up swimming and rock climbing, which I try to find time for on a daily basis.

Interests

Swimming, rock climbing, hiking, bicycling as far as healthy ones go. Beers with friends on the weekends to finish off an active week.

I want to work for a company that...

Has a mission that I believe in. A company that puts not only its employees first, but the good of its surrounding community as well. A company that strives to give and do for the people around it.

I'm making a career change because...

I want to be pushed far outside of my comfort zone and thrive. My last career change was pretty recent, but sadly has not provided me with the challenge, nor opportunities that I had hoped.

Languages spoken

Bulgarian